<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
  <language id="schinese">
    <entry id="journal_page_title_22"><![CDATA[A Beautiful Thing (1/7)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_22"><![CDATA[I am a beautiful thing, they say. Flawless as the sea of dunes. Graceful as the desert wind. Captivating as a shimmering mirage. They stare, they linger, they watch me without blinking.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_23"><![CDATA[A Beautiful Thing (2/7)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_23"><![CDATA[Such exquisiteness must be admired, they say. And so I am made to dance for their desperate, dust-pitted faces; for their watery, bloodshot eyes; their cracked, grinning lips. I am not a person to this debauched audience, I am an exotic wonder. I am a beautiful thing.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_24"><![CDATA[A Beautiful Thing (3/7)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_24"><![CDATA[Such loveliness belongs in the palace, they say. And so my hands are tied, and I am put in a caravan next to golden idols and jeweled icons. Together, we are a priceless cargo of dazzling rarities, bound for the Vizier's treasury. I know this tyrant's reputation, and I am afraid.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_25"><![CDATA[A Beautiful Thing (4/7)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_25"><![CDATA[As the wagon careens along the mountain road, I make my choice. I will not go to the Vizier. I will not be this man’s prize; his plaything. With practiced grace, I slip my bonds, and lunge for the open air. The wagon teeters and the guard shouts. Wheels lift, horses panic...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_26"><![CDATA[A Beautiful Thing (5/7)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_26"><![CDATA[I am lodged in a jumble of corpses and wreckage. My arm is pinned. The serpent appears silently from behind a rock, tongue tasting the air. The bite is quick; the venom slow. It runs cold in my veins, inching up my arm - forcing me to make a terrible choice.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_27"><![CDATA[A Beautiful Thing (6/7)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_27"><![CDATA[The knife is dull, and I must work quickly. In my panic, I saw, hack, and gouge. My cries are met with the silent indifference of the dunes, the chill of the desert wind, the cold light of the moon. I am sacrificing my beauty for a chance to live; paying for my future with the only currency I’ve ever had.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_28"><![CDATA[A Beautiful Thing (7/7)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_28"><![CDATA[I stare at my severed hand, my bloodied arm. There will be no more leering crowds, no more coins thrown at my feet. I breathe a wordless thanks to my liberator, as it slithers away into the shadows. At last, I am free of my gilded cage. At last, I finally understand: a thing cannot be truly beautiful until it is broken.]]></entry>


    <entry id="journal_page_title_29"><![CDATA[Page from a Lost Diary (1/10)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_30"><![CDATA[Page from a Lost Diary (2/10) ]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_31"><![CDATA[Page from a Lost Diary (3/10) ]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_32"><![CDATA[Page from a Lost Diary (4/10) ]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_33"><![CDATA[Page from a Lost Diary (5/10) ]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_34"><![CDATA[Page from a Lost Diary (6/10) ]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_35"><![CDATA[Page from a Lost Diary (7/10) ]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_36"><![CDATA[Page from a Lost Diary (8/10) ]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_37"><![CDATA[Page from a Lost Diary (9/10) ]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_38"><![CDATA[Page from a Lost Diary (10/10) ]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_29"><![CDATA[(The journal entry is written in a very fine and elegant cursive) To whomever may be the reader. This is a private journal. Please refrain from reading any further and return this item to its rightful owner. You may find me using the map provided. Thank you. Signed, Euryale (Attached is a detailed map of the Hamlet. However, the directions given have been smudged and are unreadable)]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_30"><![CDATA[(The journal entry is written in a very fine and elegant cursive) It's been quite some time since I've stepped foot in this grand city. Much has changed in my absence. The miserly workers had been replaced with cheerful men and women talking of the most recent battles in the king's arena. They also talk of a valiant champion who will be fighting in the arena later in the day. I tried to brush off the chatter but as I wandered about, all I heard was more and more of this man's heroic feats. With my interest peaked, I'll be making my way to the gladiatorial ring soon.]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_31"><![CDATA[(The journal entry is written in a very fine and elegant cursive) Typical. I took a wrong turn on my way to the arena and ended up in a rather droll part of the city which served as a home to many vulgar and unscrupulous individuals. It was only predictable that I would be stopped by a group of these thugs looking to strip me of my belongings. A rather poor choice of words and hands that touched places they shouldn't have resulted in an unpleasant series of events that took up more of my time than I had hoped. The praised hero would begin his fight soon so I hastily picked up my mirror and made my way to the coliseum.]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_32"><![CDATA[(The journal entry is written in a very fine and elegant cursive) I just barely made it in time for the battle. Luckily one of the guards was kind enough to procure me a seat where I could best spectate the skirmish. As the gates opened, a single man emerged and I sat amongst the crowd in awe.]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_33"><![CDATA[(The journal entry is written in a very fine and elegant cursive) The audience cheered in excitement. The warrior was the physical embodiment of perfection. His chiseled body told of a man who had seen rigorous battles while his long flowing hair would have many believe he was born from the gods. In one hand he held a fisherman's net and in the other an ornate trident. He was so perfect that I had reason to believe he had attained his beauty through obscure means, just as I had.]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_34"><![CDATA[(The journal entry is written in a very fine and elegant cursive) Amongst the crowd's cheering admiration, the hero's adversary appeared. On the opposite side of the arena, a rusted gate opened and what emerged was a behemoth pulled in chains by beastmasters. It was a creature from a children's tale. A hulking monster covered in iron spikes and decorated with scars. The citizens greeted this thing with mocking shouts and vulgar insults. Despite this menacing beast, the champion did not show an ounce of fear, but instead smirked with confidence.]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_35"><![CDATA[(The journal entry is written in a very fine and elegant cursive) The beastmasters released their chains and the battle began. At first I had my doubts. The monster was the size of ten men and shook the earth with every step. How could any man possibly hope to defeat such a thing? But to my surprise, the hero was succeeding. The fight looked more like a dance, with the agile warrior dodging the ogre's clumsy strikes. He stabbed at it with masterful precision and weaved around the behemoth as it mindlessly swung its boulder fists around in frustration.]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_36"><![CDATA[(The journal entry is written in a very fine and elegant cursive) In a spectacular display, the champion thrusted his trident into the heart of the beast, causing blood to spill forth and sending the crowd into a raucous frenzy. With a loud thud, the creature collapsed and its defiling blood soaked the soil around it. The crowd continued to cheer and applaud as the hero took in their admiration. He bravely walked to the massive corpse and planted one foot on top of its metallic head. He waved to the crowd and I could have sworn he had turned to me and winked. My heart skipped a beat.]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_37"><![CDATA[(The journal entry is written in a very fine and elegant cursive) It all happened so quickly. Our admiration quickly turned to horror as the beast revealed that it was still alive. The creature caught the hero's leg in an iron grip. It pulled the man to the ground and, with its other fist, it slammed down on the champion's face. A single scream was all we heard as the behemoth smashed the man's head and splattered bits of him all around. It slowly stood back up, covered in the gore of its victim. A moment of shock soon shifted to panic and anguish as the torn crowd began to demand justice.]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_38"><![CDATA[(The journal entry is written in a very fine and elegant cursive) The crowd entered a vengeful frenzy as they shouted for the guards. I quickly took my leave and the last thing I saw was the beast running rampant on the beastmasters that tried to subdue it. Even as I hastily made my way out of the amphitheater's gates, I could still hear the frantic shouts of the crowd and the trembling of the earth itself. It had been interesting returning to my city of origin, but I sense a riot will soon break out and I plan to depart long before it has any effect on me.]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_title_39"><![CDATA[Journal of Diana, Falconer (1/7) ]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_40"><![CDATA[Journal of Diana, Falconer (2/7) ]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_41"><![CDATA[Journal of Diana, Falconer (3/7) ]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_42"><![CDATA[Journal of Diana, Falconer (4/7) ]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_43"><![CDATA[Journal of Diana, Falconer (5/7) ]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_44"><![CDATA[Journal of Diana, Falconer (6/7) ]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_45"><![CDATA[Journal of Diana, Falconer (7/7) ]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_39"><![CDATA[I've been told that keeping a journal can help take my mind off the lingering dread that this wretched place can invite, so I might as well start now. We have been tasked with exploring a portion of the wealds, a place that brings back many unpleasant memories but one that I know better than anyone. I will be accompanied by Turid and Aldwin. While Turid can be brash sometimes and Aldwin reckless, they make for an effective and reliable crew. Also assigned to us is a new face, one that troubles me...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_40"><![CDATA[We've embarked on our mission and I've already got a bad feeling. Not one hour from leaving and the new blood is already complaining. Too much walking she says, too much dirt she says. Worst is she comes to the expedition dressed in a fancy robe and wielding a broken mirror. What's her reasoning for such strange equipment? She says its "comfortable". I'll never understand these city-folk...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_41"><![CDATA[Our first encounter in this wretched place almost ended in disaster, but the recruit pulled through. Turns out she's some witch, using her broke mirror to conjure some healing magic. Made Turid right as rain when he got stabbed by some cultist. Aldwin has taken a liking to her, but I've grown suspicious...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_42"><![CDATA[Everything is going smoothly. I sit and write this as we rest by the campfire. The witch lady is trading compliments with Turid, some rubbish I'll never understand. Have to admit, even for a damsel raised in the cities, she is extraordinarily beautiful. Flawless skin with a soothing voice. The only thing wrong is that damn mirror of hers. Shattered and scratched up like its older than her. Very strange...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_43"><![CDATA[Damn brigands ambushed us in the night. Different lot than the one I used to run with but their behaviour was no different. Poor Aldwin was the first victim, one of the brutes stabbed him right in the gut and sliced him open. He died laying in a pool of his own blood. Before I could even grab my bow, one of their rangers blasted my arm. Completely mangled, I'll be no use to anyone in this state. They went straight for the witch, poor thing had just woken up. I thought that'd be the end for her but I couldn't be more wrong...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_44"><![CDATA[The damned witch dropped her mirror to reveal her hideous form. A mess of tentacle, maw, and spit, screeching at her would-be assailants. Turid ran screaming just from the sight of the thing. When one of the cutthroats took a swing at the creature, it moved with impossible speed and vomited a putrid bile from its many mouthes. The poor fools screamed in agony as their flesh melted from their bones until all that remained was a puddle of boiling blood. That alone was enough to send the whole band of thugs running, and in that moment the monstrosity turned its gaze to me. Pure instinct kicked in and I ran as fast as I could into the darkness...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_45"><![CDATA[The wound is infected. I'm having hallucinations. My damned bird flew away during that terrible encounter and hasn't returned. I can only assume Turid has suffered the same fate as Aldwin. To think this is the way it would end, huddled under a tree haunted by the memories of that unspeakable creature. I thought I'd be redeemed for my sins, but instead I die forgotten like so many other countless souls. I thought I was ready to fight the horrors, but now I know better...]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_title_46"><![CDATA[MISSING]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_47"><![CDATA[MISSING]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_48"><![CDATA[MISSING]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_49"><![CDATA[MISSING]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_50"><![CDATA[MISSING]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_51"><![CDATA[MISSING]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_52"><![CDATA[MISSING]]></entry>

	<entry id="journal_page_text_46"><![CDATA[MISSING]]></entry>
	<entry id="journal_page_text_47"><![CDATA[MISSING]]></entry>
	<entry id="journal_page_text_48"><![CDATA[MISSING]]></entry>
	<entry id="journal_page_text_49"><![CDATA[MISSING]]></entry>
	<entry id="journal_page_text_50"><![CDATA[MISSING]]></entry>
	<entry id="journal_page_text_51"><![CDATA[MISSING]]></entry>
	<entry id="journal_page_text_52"><![CDATA[MISSING]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_title_53"><![CDATA[Journal of Mathas, Witch Hunter (1/8)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_54"><![CDATA[Journal of Mathas, Witch Hunter (2/8)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_55"><![CDATA[Journal of Mathas, Witch Hunter (3/8)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_56"><![CDATA[Journal of Mathas, Witch Hunter (4/8)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_57"><![CDATA[Journal of Mathas, Witch Hunter (5/8)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_58"><![CDATA[Journal of Mathas, Witch Hunter (6/8)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_59"><![CDATA[Journal of Mathas, Witch Hunter (7/8)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_60"><![CDATA[Journal of Mathas, Witch Hunter (8/8)]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_53"><![CDATA[I tracked my latest hunt to the grand city. This one will be illusive, its behaviour suggests that it prefers manipulation over direct confrontation. It'll be difficult to identify the creature, given the degeneracy of this city's populace, but I will not give up my search. The Light guides me.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_54"><![CDATA[I've found the hag. I over-estimated its intelligence, it had made itself easy to find based on its arrogant nature and abhorrent flaunting. I've announced its debaucheries to the entirety of the city populace and the hunt will soon begin.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_55"><![CDATA[The creature fled into the foul shantytowns that sit in the city's shadow. I cannot allow such a thing to exist, so I set the entirety of the corrupted dwellings ablaze. With nowhere to run, it will surely burn for its sins.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_56"><![CDATA[Many charred corpses were found amongst the aftermath. They are unrecognizable but I am sure that the witch can be included among them. Despite my radical actions, the cityfolk do not seem to care for those lost in the fire. Surely they must understand as I do that the loss of these peasants is a small price to pay for the eradication of evil. And so, with another monster put down for good, I continue my crusade against corruption.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_57"><![CDATA[This will surely mark me down in the manuscripts as a hero of the Light! We have captured the heretical witch that had splintered our faith. I will be responsible for her execution, and there is no punishment more fitting for a false prophet than death by holy fire.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_58"><![CDATA[To see the witch with my own eyes is to know pure corruption. There is no doubt that this thing is responsible for splitting the faithful followers of the Light into conflicted factions. It speaks as if it is a disciple of the Light like us, but I see through her ruse. I will commence the burning shortly.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_59"><![CDATA[It is an abomination unlike any I've encountered! It extinguished the sanctioned fires of the pyre with ease and presented itself as an avatar of the Flame. It had converted all around me to its falsified fate and I watched in horror as both peasants and crusaders of the Light bowed in unison to this creature of debased prophecies. I retreated from its deformed presence, and now I must warn those that are still pure of its corrupting nature.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_60"><![CDATA[The worst thing has come to reality. The creature proved too strong, and now all have come to worship it as a demigod. I have been excommunicated from what was once a faith that fought the darkness but now is a cult praising a thing that mockingly resembles an angel. Even in the face of defeat, I will not stop my hunt. This thing must die, or mankind will be damned for eternity.]]></entry>
  </language>
</root>

